# RODRIGO LOPEZ RAZO

Full Stack Developer Lead

Full Stack software developer with about 12 years' experience on backend and frontend development. Across my experience as developer I have developed a high sense of urgency, I have worked for companies where it is necessary to solve an issue in minutes, this has led me to have a great experience with errors or problems in production. I like to be updated with the new technologies for web applications or mobile applications. Currently I'm as leader of multicultural team. I always try to have a good communication with team to reach the objectives of project.

## | EDUCATION

Universidad de la salle Bajio (2005 - 2009) Computer and systems engineering

### **WORKING EXPERIENCES**

SolutionStream (December 2022– Present day)

#### Sr. Full Stack Developer Lead

Technology Stack: Vuejs, Spring Boot Java, Typescript, Google GCP, JavaScript

Project: Video Game Element United (https://www.elementunited.com/)

Project Description: Part of the development of this project I have had to be the team leader, achieving objectives that had not been previously obtained. The goal of this project is for the player to advance in the game and get cryptocurrencies according to their performance.

- Development of platform Front End for the video game
- Create the API on spring boot
- Manage de PR (check and approve) on GitLab

M6Connect (Oct 2020 – December 2022)

#### Sr. Full Stack Developer Lead

Technology Stack: Vuejs, Laravel, Lumen, NodeJs, AWS (S3,Lambda Functions), Javascript

#### Project: M6 Platform

Project Description: Develop of process-oriented platform for hospitals:

- Development of platform developers.m6connect.com
- Create components for specific functionality on platform as ex. Feed as Facebook/Twitter/Linkedin
- Development and implementation of Restful Web APIs, and exposes endpoints using HTTP verbs like GET, PUT,
  POST and DELETE with nodejs/Laravel/lumen
- Deploys and Pull request review on Git hub
- Taking of requirements
- Leader of Developers and manage the team.

All projects where under git version control

### Instituto Lux (OCt 2014 – Oct 2020)

## **I Software Developer Lead**

Technology Stack: .Net, Vue.js, SQL, HTML5, Javascript

- Development Web Application for Register of new members(made With VueJS +
- Laravel) https://lux.org.mx/admisiones/#/
- Develoment Web Application to Instituto Lux College for Child delivery (intranet)
- made with VueJs + Laravel
- Development of the current landing page (php-mysql, responsive) with panel http://institutolux.edu.mx
- administration.
- Development of help desk for tickets support (php-mysql)
- Development of application for rating capture BADyG's evaluation (C# MCV)
- Improvement and administration of the school's web and office control system
- Improvement and administration of the institute's cash control system.
- Administration of domain and mail of the institute (platform google).

Siemens (Apr. 2014 –Oct 2014)

### I Sr. Software Developer

Technology Stack: .Net, asp.net, SQL, DevExpress

• Web application development for the administration of computer equipment (Register, Low, Reservation, Assignment of equipment) developed in C #, SQL Server 2008, WCF)

## Calzado Andrea (Aug. 2012 – Apr. 2014)

#### I Sr. Software Developer

Technology Stack: .Net, asp.net, SQL, DevExpress

- Development of WCF Services for sending e-mail to Andrea
- System Customers.
- Development of WCF Services for billing through a Supplier's DLL (MySuite).
- Development and improvements to the sales system.

### Poder Judicial del Estado de Guanajuato (March. 2009 – Aug. 2012)

#### I Webmaster

Technology Stack: .Net, asp.net, SQL, Mysql, PHP, C#, WCF

- Updating of the page design of www.poderjudicial-gto.gob.mx (Years of update:2009,
- 2011, 2012)
- Development of a portal for mobile devices for the consultation of court recordsand
- Chambers.
- Improvement in the publication of Court Agreements for consultation from the
- website.
- New service for the Consultation of Edicts from the portal.
- New Service to display the index of the digitized file.
- New Service for the printing of data sheet for stagecoaches.
- New virtual Platform for the internal and external use with technology Asp.Net, WCF, Jquery.
- Mantenaince & backup database

# SKILLS

Operating systems: MS-Windows, Centos 7

Backend Development: Spring Boot Java, NodeJS, Laravel, Lumen, .NET C# WCF

Frontend Development: VueJS, React, React Native

Databases: MySQL, SQL Server

Tools and platforms: AWS, GCP

# | LANGUAGES

Spanish (Native)

English (Professional Proficiency)